

AMAN KUMAR SAH

Computer Science Student

As an IT student and creator, I bring a wealth of expertise in public speaking, team management, content development, and social media. With a strong technical background and a passion for innovation, I am driven to make a significant impact in the ever-evolving field of technology

Contact

977-9804806530

amanshah0844@gmail.com

shah098.wordpress.com

Thapagaun, New Baneshwor

Education

Bachelor of Science(Hons)

Herald College Kathmandu 2022-Present Naxal, Kathmandu

Higher Seconday Education

Shree Ram lagan Secondary School 2008-2021 Haripur, Sarlahi

Skills

Organized

Communication

Teamwork

Meeting deadlines

Critical thinking

Experience

Social Media Manager

Creators Community

Jan 2022 - Present

Responsible for developing and implementing social media strategies, creating content, engaging with followers, analyzing data and insights, and managing online advertising campaigns to effectively promote brands or organizations on social media platforms.

Marketer (Leader Project Forum)

NYEF(Nepalese Young Entreprnerurship Forum April 2023- May 2023

Learn customer service techniques, product knowledge, professional presentation, handling difficult situations, team collaboration, and continuous improvement in greeting training.

Volunteering

Vision Quest (Herald Dev Corp)

Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

An entrepreneurship program designed to empower +2 students in building their entrepreneurial skills and ventures, providing guidance, resources, and support to cultivate the next generation of innovative and successful entrepreneurs.

Language

Nepali English Hindi

Reference

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/a mansahcode